freetvmov.com 2019-02-11

# Privacy Policy & Cookies

## Privacy Policy & Cookies

This website privacy policy describes how **freetvmov.com** protects and makes use of the information you give the company when you use this website. If you are asked to provide information when using this website, it will only be used in the ways described in this privacy policy. This policy is updated from time to time. The latest version is published on this page.

This website privacy policy was updated on: 24/05/2017

If you have any questions about this policy, write us in the contact page.  

### **  
Introduction**

We gather and use certain information about individuals in order to provide products and services and to enable certain functions on this website. We also can collect information to better understand how visitors use this website and to present timely, relevant information to them.  

### **  
How we use this data**

Collecting this data helps us understand what you are looking from the company, enabling us to deliver improved products and services. Specifically, we may use data:

To contact you in response to a specific enquiry - The information does not stored on any database, the administration of the website will get an email with your details that you provide at the contact form.

### **  
Ip numbers**

Whenever You use our Service by leaving a comment, we read the IP number of Your network, we do not permanently store the data nor make it available to the public, We store part of the IP for our spam detect and may use to this part ip publicly.

### **Links from our site**

Our website may contain links to other websites. Please note that we have no control of websites outside the **freetvmov.com** domain. If you provide information to a website to which we link, we are not responsible for its protection and privacy. Always be wary when submitting data to websites. Read the site’s data protection and privacy policies fully.

### **Cookies and how we use them**

We use so-called cookies to allocate your requests from the internet. These small files are automatically stored on your hard drive by your browser for the duration of your stay on our website and are necessary for the accurate use of our website. You can delete the cookies after finishing your stay at our website with certain configurations in your browser. They serve to make our website more user-friendly, effective and secure.

[You can find further information on the subject of cookies here](http://www.aboutcookies.org/default.aspx)

Our online offerings are also usable under exclusion of cookies. If you do not want cookies to be stored on your computer, you can deactivate the corresponding option in the system settings of your browser. Saved cookies can be deleted in the system settings of the browser. The exclusion of cookies can lead to functional restrictions of this online offer.

The option to have many online advertising cookies from companies is given via the US website http://www.aboutads.info/choices or the European website [http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad- choices/](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-%20choices/)

Most internet browsers accept cookies automatically, but you can change the settings of your browser to erase cookies or prevent automatic acceptance if you prefer.

These links explain how you can control cookies via your browser - remember that if you turn off cookies in your browser then these settings apply to all websites not just this one:

  * **Internet Explorer** [http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835](https://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835) (this page links to further information for different versions of IE - the mobile version is at [http:/ /www.microsoft.com/windowsphone/en-us/howto/wp7/web/changing-privacy-and-other-browser-settings.aspx](https://www.microsoft.com/windowsphone/en-us/howto/wp7/web/changing-privacy-and-other-browser-settings.aspx)).
  * **Chrome:** [http://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en-GB&answer=95647](https://support.google.com/chrome/bin/answer.py?hl=en-GB&answer=95647)
  * **Safari:** [http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/5.0/en/9277.html](http://docs.info.apple.com/article.html?path=Safari/5.0/en/9277.html) (or [http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677](https://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677)for mobile versions)
  * **Firefox:** [http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/ Enabling%20and%20disabling%20cookies](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/Enabling%20and%20disabling%20cookies)
  * **Blackberries:** [http://docs.blackberry.com/en/smartphone_users/deliverables/ 32004/Turn_off_cookies_in_the_browser_60_1072866_11.jsp](http://docs.blackberry.com/en/smartphone_users/deliverables/32004/Turn_off_cookies_in_the_browser_60_1072866_11.jsp)
  * **Android:** [http://support.google.com/mobile/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=169022](https://support.google.com/mobile/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=169022)
  * **Opera:** [http://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/](https://www.opera.com/browser/tutorials/security/privacy/)

#### Types of cookie that may be used during your visit to the Website:

The following types of cookie are used on this site. We don't list every single cookie used by name - but for each type of cookie we tell you how you can control its use.

**Use of Google Analytics**

**freetvmov.com** uses Google Analytics, which is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc., (“Google”), 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.

Web analysis is the collection, storage and analysis of data about the behavior of visitors to websites. A web analysis service collects data including from which website an affected person has come to a website (so-called referrers), which subpages of the website were accessed or how often and for which length of stay a subpage was viewed. A web analysis is mainly used to optimize a website and for the cost-benefit analysis of online advertising.

We only use Google Analytics with active IP anonymization. This means that the IP address of the users Google within member states of the European Union or in other contracting states of the Agreement from the European Economic Area will be shortened. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be sent to a Google server in the US and shortened there.

Google is certified under the Privacy Shield Agreement and therefore provides a guarantee to comply with European privacy legislation: [https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active)

Google Analytics uses so-called “cookies”, which are text files that are stored on your computer and make it possible for us to analyse your use of this website. The information about your use of this website that is generated by means of a cookie is, in most cases, transferred to a Google server in the USA and stored there. However, if IP anonymization is activated on this website and you are located in a member state of the European Union or in another contracting state to the Agreement on the European Economic Area, your IP address will first be shortened by Google.

Only in exceptional cases will your complete IP address be transferred to a Google server in the USA and shortened there. Google will use this information on behalf of the operator of this website in order to analyze your use of this website, compile reports on website activities, and render further services related to website and internet usage for the operator of this website.

The IP address provided by your browser in the context of Google Analytics will not be merged by Google with other data. You can prevent storage of cookies by means of a setting in your browser software; however, we must advise you that in this case you might not be able to use all the functions of this website to their full extent.

Beyond this, you can also prevent collection of the data that is generated by cookies and related to your use of this website (including your IP address) by Google as well as processing of this data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plugin available under the following link. [http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). We like to point out, however, that in this case you might not be able to use all the website’s functions to their full extent. By using our website, you agree to the processing of the compiled data by Google in the aforementioned manner and for the aforementioned purpose.

For more information about Google’s use of data, opt-out and other options, please visit Google’s websites:

**Advertising Partners**

Some of our affiliates may use cookies and web beacons. Our advertising partner is Google Adsense.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology for advertisements and links that appear on freetvmov.com and are sent directly to your browser. This automatically gives you your IP address. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) can also be used by third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising or to personalize the ad content displayed.

The collection and processing of data is based on the legitimate interest in accordance with Article 6 s. 1 f of the GDPR and by commissioning the processing of data by advertising partners (third parties) with a concluded DAV / DPA („data processing contract“) pursuant to Art. 28 GDPR. freetvmov.com has no access or control over these third-party cookies.

Refer to the Affiliate’s Privacy Policy for details on their practices and how to opt out of specific practices. The freetvmov.com privacy policy does not apply to other advertisers or sites, and we cannot control their activities.

If you want to disable cookies, you can do so through your own browser options. You can find more detailed information about cookie management with certain web browsers on the respective websites of the browsers.

**Use of Google AdSense / Doubleclick**

**freetvmov.com** uses Google Adsense, an advertisement service of Google Inc., Mountain View, USA („Google“). Google Adsense uses „Cookies“ which are stored by your browser (e.g. as small text files) on your computer and which allow an analysis of your usage of this website. Google Adsense also uses so-called „Web Beacons“ (little invisible images) to collect information. By using Web Beacons simple actions like visitor traffic on the website may be recorded and collected. The information about your usage of the website generated by the cookies and/or Web Beacons (including your IP address) will be transmitted to a server of Google in the United States of America and will be stored there. You can prevent the storage of cookies in your browser.

Information collected by Google may be shared with third parties, by contract or by law, by Google. Google will not connect your IP address with other data you have stored.

With the corresponding settings on your web browser you can prevent the mentioned cookies from being stored on your PC. However, there is the possibility that the contents of this website can no longer be used to the same extent. By using this site, you consent to the processing of personal data by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

[Further information on the privacy policy of Google AdSense can be found here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

Here, you can disable Googe AdSense Cookies: [https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous) and [https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

**Google Library for Ajax and jQuery**

We use Ajax and jQuery’s JavaScript library to optimize the webpage’s loading rate. In this case, program libraries are retrieved from servers of the company Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (Google) specifically the Google CDN. If you have already used jQuery on another page of the Google CDN, your browser will use the cached copy. Otherwise, the required information will be downloaded. In doing so, your visited website will be sent to the Google server. Also, the IP address of your device is stored by Google. For more information, please visit: [https://cloud.google.com/cdn/?hl=en](https://cloud.google.com/cdn/?hl=en) and [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/?hl=en](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/?hl=en). To prevent the execution of JavaScript, you can install a JavaScript Blocker.

**Google Maps**

We use the Google Maps service provided by Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA, to illustrate the location of addresses. The privacy policy can be found at: [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and the opt-out at: [https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated).

**Third-party service cookies**

Social sharing, video and other services we offer are run by other companies. These companies may drop cookies on your computer when you use them on our site or if you are already logged in to them.

Here is a list of places where you can find out more about specific services that we may use and their use of cookies:

  * **Facebook's** data use policy: [http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other)
  * **AddThis** (the service that runs some of our social sharing buttons): [http://www.addthis.com/privacy#.T6j--usS0bw](https://www.addthis.com/privacy#.T6j--usS0bw)
  * **Twitter's** privacy policy: [https://twitter.com/privacy](https://twitter.com/privacy)

**Site management cookies**

These are used to maintain your identity or session on the Website. For instance, where our websites run on more than one server, we use a cookie to ensure that you are sent information by one specific server (otherwise you may log in or out unexpectedly). We may use similar cookies when you vote in opinion polls to ensure that you can only vote once, and to ensure that you can use our commenting functionality when not logged in (to ensure you don't see comments you've reported as abusive, for instance, or don't vote comments up/down more than once).

These cookies cannot be turned off individually but you could change your browser setting to refuse all cookies (see above) if you do not wish to accept them.

**SSL Encryption**

freetvmov.com uses SSL encryption for security and to protect the transmission of sensitive content, such as the requests you send to the site operator. You can recognize an encrypted connection by changing the address line of the browser from „http://“ to „https://“ and the lock symbol in your browser bar.

If SSL encryption is enabled, the data you submit to us cannot be read by third parties.

**Right of Information**

We are not store any personal information but because other users can post a comment - you can ask to delete this comment with the “Report spam“ button. We not store any data that you can't see on our website.  If you have further questions regarding the privacy policy or need more information on a certain point, you can contact our data protection officer at **infoATfreetvmov.com** (replace AT with a @).

##
